(MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
TRAVIS: Wiener.
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
HARRISON: Wiener.
TRAVIS: Boobs.
HARRISON: Boobs.
TRAVIS: Pussy.
HARRISON: Pussy.
Damn.
God damn.
Ass.
Asshole.
Ass face.
How far do you
think we've gone?
Uh...
Fifty miles.
I think we're almost
to the woods. Come on.
Don't get rust poisoning.
TRAVIS: Come on!
I thought it was an arrowhead.
TRAVIS: Bitch.
HARRISON: Bitch.
TRAVIS: Shit.
HARRISON: Shit.
TRAVIS: Shithead.
Shithead.
Fuck.
Say it. Fuck.
That's the worst cuss.
Actually my friend,
he's in eighth grade,
he says that it's just a
different language from Russia.
So it's fine to say it.
Oh, look!
What? Snake hole!
I'm going to leave mine in there
in case they try to escape.
(GRUNTS) Good idea.
(LAUGHING)
Want to see a magic trick?
No way!
Want some?
Yeah!
We gotta ration it, though.
Okay.
Two centimeters each a day.
Wait, why don't you
keep it in your pocket?
Pickpockets.
Got my wallet in here, too.
(cows MOOING)
The creek should be right over...
Get down!
What?
It's the cops!
We haven't even
been gone that long.
You're right.
Did they see us?
I don't think so.
We can distract them.
Throw this on the far side
to make a noise.
Oh, crap!
You hit it!
Oh, shit!
Shit! I hit a cop car!
Let's go!
Wait, wait, wait! It has
my fingerprints on it.
Mine, too.
Okay. Go get it.
No way!
Fine. Chicken.
Wait.
Go that way.
It's better camouflage.
There's no one in there.
They could be hiding.
My dad says sometimes cops put
empty cop cars near roads
so that people won't speed, 'cause
they think they're real cop cars.
But there's no road.
Do you see it?
I don't know.
It could be any of them.
Come on, let's just go.
I dare you to touch it.
The cop car?
No way!
If I do it, you have to do it.
Okay.
Ready?
Stay low just in case
they're hiding.
Now!
Okay.
(PANTING) Your turn.
(WHISPERING) Oh, crap. Oh, crap.
Oh, crap. Oh, crap.
Oh, crap.
Come on, come on. Come on!
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLING)
(DOOR HANDLE CLICKING)
(TRAVIS GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(THUD)
No way!
Quick, get in!
Get in!
Nuh-uh.
Why? Look.
So?
(MIMICS DRIVING)
Hit the boosters!
(CONTINUES MIMICKING)
TRAVIS: There's a lot of
bad guys behind us!
HARRISON: I'll shoot 'em!
(IMITATING GUN FIRING)
Did you kill them?
Look out!
Aah! You're driving us
right off of a cliff! No!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(MIMICS CRASHING)
(KEYS JANGLE)
Where's the siren?
We need to
get out of this lava!
Holy shit!
No way.
Which one?
The big one?
It fits.
Do you know how to drive?
Yeah, I know. Mario Kart.
Yeah, me too.
(SOFT CLICKING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Whoa!
(DOOR ALARM BEEPING)
(ENGINE IDLING)
Me first! Wait!
(DOOR ALARM STOPS)
Try this one.
(ENGINE REVS)
Awesome!
Why isn't it going?
Uh...
It's moving.
It's moving! Quick, get in.
We're going to get in trouble.
We already ran away.
It doesn't matter.
What if someone sees us?
(TIRES SCREECH)
We'll just tell them
we're cops.
Good idea.
This is our cop car now.
HARRISON: Oh, oh, Oh!
TRAVIS: Oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit!
Oh, shit!
TRAVIS: Oh, Shit! Oh, Shit!
HARRISON: Oh! (LAUGHS)
TRAVIS: That was so cool.
(SIREN WAILING DIFFERENT TUNES)
TRAVIS: This is our cop car!
This is our cop car!
This is our cop car! (REWING)
(LIQUID SLOSHING)
(WHISTLES)
(GRUNTING)
(KICKING)
(GRUNTS)
(FLIES BUZZING)
Fuck. Shit.
(GRUNTS)
(THUD)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SNIFFS)
(LINE RINGING)
Hello, hey. Hey. Hey there.
Hey there, Miranda.
Hello, Miranda.
Hey. Hello, there.
(RINGING CONTINUES)
Dispatch. Hey there, Miranda.
Mitch Kretzer.
Hey there, Sheriff.
Everything okay?
It's been better, I'm afraid.
Oh, no. What's wrong?
Well, I seem to be having
some trouble with my radio.
Not sure what it is.
Is this the one
in your patrol car,
or the one you go!
In your truck?
Patrol car. Some kind of odd
interference I'm getting,
maybe a trucker channel
cutting through.
Or those boys out east with their
remote control airplanes. Who knows?
Anything odd on your end?
No. Not that I can think of.
I tried lo radio in
to y'all ladies.
(STAMMERS)
You didn't hear that?
Oh, no-Must not be
coming through.
(SCOFFS)
I see that
I thought y'all was just
giving me the cold shoulder.
(LAUGHS) Never, Sheriff.
Okay, well, I'm gonna see if
it's a short in the receiver,
and in the meantime,
if you do need to reach me,
why don't you just go ahead
and call me on my cell?
Are you sure you don't want me
to send Gary down there
to have a look?
No. No. I'm gonna see if I can
handle this one by myself.
All righty.
Thank you kindly.
Have a good day.
Any games?
HARRISON: Eh, nah.
(WHISPERS) Whoa.
(BURPS)
Oh! Now me!
FEMALE DISPATCHER: Last car, repeat.
(GASPS)
What should I say?
Be quiet! Shh!
They can't hear unless
I push down the button.
I know.
Say, "Cops are, cops are..."
"Cops drink
diarrhea milkshakes."
Cops drink diarrhea milkshakes
and then poop double diarrhea.
(LAUGHS)
Say, "Shit!" Okay.
FEMALE DISPATCHER: This is Dispatch.
Please repeat.
Wait, but they're gonna
know we're not cops.
Yeah, you're right. They probably
know all the cops' voices.
Can I drive?
(MOOING)
TRAVIS: It keeps going when Hake
my foot off the thing. Look.
HARRISON: Why's it doing that?
I don't know.
HARRISON: I know. You
jump out and run around,
and I'll scoot over and
be like, "Hurry! Get in!"
TRAVIS: Okay.
One, two, three! Go!
(GRUNTS)
HARRISON: That was awesome!
(PANTING)
TRAVIS: There's a lot of
stuff back here.
What do I do? What?
Look.
Whoa, that's a real road.
We can go way faster
on the real road.
Should I crash
through the gate?
Mmm... Nah.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I'll get in.
(YELLING)
Shit.
Did that break it?
It must be titanium.
(GRUNTING)
Can you open the lock?
No.
Try hitting it with the car.
Okay.
(ENGINE REWING)
It's working.
A little further.
I'm pushing as hard as I can.
It's working. Put your
foot down all the...
HARRISON: Whoa!
Serious shit!
Oh, shit!
(DOOR CLOSES)
That was awesome!
Yeah, that was so awesome.
Let's see how fast we can go.
Uh... Yeah, okay.
Okay. Get it all
the way up to the 100.
How fast am I going now?
Let me try.
HARRISON: It still won't stop.
TRAVIS: Oh, I know.
Hold on to that shifter thingy.
Okay. (DOOR ALARM BEEPING)
HARRISON: Whoa!
TRAVIS: Okay, "R" means go
backwards and "P" means stop.
(DOOR ALARM STOPS)
HARRISON: Makes sense.
This is so awesome!
(ACCELERATING)
HARRISON: Look out!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
TRAVIS: Yeah!
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(WINDOW SQUEAKING)
(DOOR SLAMS DISTANTLY)
MAN: Fuck you, Marcie!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SOFTLY) Yeah. Come on, bitch,
get on there, get on there.
Come on. Come on.
Get on, bitch.
Get on.
Okay, baby.
Okay, come to Daddy.
Come on now.
(EXCLAIMS IN FRUSTRATION)
(DOGS BARKING)
Oh, come on, baby.
Come on, get on there. Get...
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(SIREN WAILING)
(LINE RINGING)
Dispatch. Miranda. Mitch again.
Hey there, Sheriff.
Any luck with that radio?
I'll tell you what, you haven't
missed a thing. It's been...
Hey' we got any units
in the Jefferson Area?
Lei me check.
Yeah, I think I might
have a 211 in progress,
suspect on foot
somewhere in the vicinity...
In the vicinity of Widefield
Drive and Imperial.
Can you call that in
for me'? Code 3.
Sorry, Sheriff. I didn't catch
that last part, Widefield and...
Widefield Drive
and Imperial. Code 3.
Roll the window down, sir.
License, registration,
proof of insurance, please.
(GROANS)
ls there a problem?
I'm gonna need you to step out
of the car for me, please, sir.
MIRANDA: (OVER RADIO) Calling all units.
There's a 211 in progress.
Suspect on foot. Near Widefield
and imperial. Code 3.
OFFICER: Dispatch, this is 55.
I am 10-95 at
Imperial and Cherokee.
I can cover on that.
Just sit tight. I only need
to see your registration.
MIRANDA: Fifty-five, copy.
Proceed to Widefield and Imperial.
Code 3.
Ten-four.
Get those tags changed.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(MUSIC PLAYING SOFTLY)
How are you doing today, ma'am?
I'm good. Yourself?
I'm fine. Kind of slow.
(SCOFFS)
I swear I think I just saw the
craziest thing out there.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
(BELL JINGLES)
FEMALE HOSTESS: Well,
you want to come pick up?
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Okay, what would you like?
Okay, enjoy your lunch.
Thank you.
Bye. Okay, thank you.
Excuse me. Officers?
(RADIO STATIC CRACKLING)
MAN: (OVER RADIO)
More than anyone.
Daniel prophesied
those who arrive
will go to everlasting Hie
or everlasting death.
(TURNS RADIO OFF)
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
(LINE RINGING)
MIRANDA: Mitch. We're starting to get
some radio interference now, too.
Yeah. I'm having a hell
of a time with my radio.
It could be.
It's the damnedest thing.
We just got a report of a
stolen sheriff's cruiser.
A what?
It could be what's
causing the interference.
Yeah, but everyone is
accounted for, right?
Of course. It's just,
this lady is sure
she saw two kids driving
a cruiser out on 110.
Two kids. How old?
She says under ten.
(LAUGHING)
Under ten.
Well, Miranda,
I think we can...
I think we can go ahead and
throw that one in the nut file,
since everyone's accounted for.
Oi course.
But I'll tell you what.
How about we all switch
over to Channel Seven
until we get this sorted out?
Well, we normally keep Channel
Seven open just in case...
(RADIO STATIC CRACKLING)
There it is again.
Just for my own peace of mind.
I hear you. I'll switch the
rest of the boys over to Seven.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just... Just to be safe.
Attention all units,
10-6 to Channel Seven.
please 10-6
to Channel Seven
until further notice.
Please confirm.
MALE OFFICER 1: This is 55,
switching to Channel Seven.
MALE OFFICER 2: This is 37,
FEMALE OFFICER 3: Forty-five,
switching to Channel Seven.
(STATIC)
MIRANDA: Please repeat.
MALE OFFICER 42 This is unit
21, switching to Seven.
Seventeen.
MALE OFFICER 5:
Dispatch, this is 17,
switching over
to Channel Seven.
MIRANDA: Confirmed. Dispatch
switching over to Channel Seven.
(RADIO SWITCHES OFF)
(DOGS BARKING)
Hello, ladies.
Hush. Hush. I said, "Hush."
Hey. Hey.
(DOGS PANTING)
(WHIMPERING)
All right, kids. Fun's over.
I know who you are.
And you are in a whole hell
of a lot of trouble.
Do you understand?
It's downright stupid
to steal a police car,
but you've done it.
And what's done is done.
What we're looking at
is a felony offense.
A felony offense.
And what that means is
guaranteed jail time.
The only thing
that can help you now
is if that car is returned
to me in one piece.
And what that means
is you ski}! Have a chance
to work something out,
I! You tell me
right now where you are.
Do you understand?
Keep going.
A little further.
Oh, perfect, right there.
On three.
One!
Two!
Aim for the vest.
Two and a half!
Two and three quarters!
Now!
(GUN CLICKING)
Ah, shit.
Maybe it's out of bullets.
I think the trigger's stuck.
Where's the little gun?
Uh...
I don't know.
I'll go get some more bullets.
Okay.
What do you think this does?
Uh...
I don't know.
(DEFIBRILLATOR POWERING UP)
SHERIFF KRETZER:
(OVER RADIO) Once again,
to the two children
who have stolen my vehicle.
This does not have to
be a felony offense.
Heck, it doesn't even
have to be a misdemeanor.
What's impatient is that the car
gets returned to me, immediately.
(PANTING)
What?
If you do not know how to
use the radio, it's easy.
You just pick up the mic, and you
hold down the little black button
and you can talk, and when you're
through, you let go and I can talk.
And no one else can hear.
This doesn't have to be...
I just want my car back.
We should get out of here.
Yeah, I'll go get the stuff.
No! What?
I mean leave the car.
What? Why?
'Cause we're in big trouble.
We're not in trouble.
You're just too scared to drive
fast enough to get away from them.
I drive fast!
You don't drive fast.
I saw you.
You were only going 35, pussy.
No, I'm not! I was
driving as fast as you.
Grandma's boy.
Hey! Screw you!
Don't push me! (GRUNTS)
I'm gonna leave and you can go
to jail when the cops get here.
I'm not going to jail.
Why not?
(SOFT SHUFFLING)
(THUMP)
MAN: Don't kill me, my God!
God! Please don't kill me.
It wasn't our fault.
I'll do anything.
I'll fucking do anything.
I'll fucking do anything,
just don't kill me.
Don't fucking kill me.
Wait. It wasn't our fault.
I told you.
I told you it wasn't
(MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
"Dude, we got to do it now,"
and he said, "No."
My brother,
where's my brother? You fuck.
You fuck. You don't...
You fuck.
You killed him. Don't kill me.
Don't kill me, don't kill me.
(MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
Do it! Do it!
(WHIMPERING)
Are you a bad guy?
I'm a good guy-
I'm a good... I'm a good guy.
Then why are you tied up?
(WHIMPERS)
Um...
Because I, uh...
I need someone to rescue me.
You boys are gonna
rescue me, right?
Maybe.
You know who the bad guy is?
The sheriff.
He's a bad, bad guy.
Where is he?
Whoa, wait, hey.
Hey, don't leave me in here!
Hey!
The fuck?
Fuck, don't leave me!
I think he's a good guy.
Yeah, me too.
Okay. Let's let him out.
Listen up.
We're gonna let you out,
but you got to promise
that you won't tell on us.
Of course. I swear.
You can't tell my
grandma or his mom
or any of our teachers.
Or my step-dad, Chris.
I won't tell him.
I won't tell a soul.
Ow. (GRUNTS)
Fuck. Ow.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
This one's really tight. Yeah.
I think you need to cut 'em.
All right?
Maybe we can shoot them off.
No! No, no, no! Don't...
Don't do that. All right'?
Hey. Hey, come here.
You know what'?
I'm looking at you boys.
You seem tough.
You probably...
You must have a knife, right?
Maybe a pocket knife on you?
I had one, but it got taken
away from me at school.
How about you, you got a knife?
Well, there must be
something sharp around here.
Go on and take a look.
You, take a look.
Yeah, there might be
something sharp in here.
Maybe later, we got to go.
No, no, don't. Please.
I need you. I need you.
Look, this really hurts.
And if you don't get me out,
I might die.
We can look.
Take a look. You stay here.
Hey. Y'all best friends?
How old are you?
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(SOFTLY) I'm so glad to see you
boys instead of that sheriff.
He's a really, really bad guy.
Believe me.
I'm going to hook you...
HARRISON: I found one!
The tweezers and
the toothpick are missing,
but it's got the knife part.
That's great. Just come here.
Come here. Get to cutting.
(LOW) Listen, okay?
You can't have this cop car.
It's our cop car.
We found it, and we're not going
to let you have it. Okay?
Deal.
Don't worry, you can have it.
I don't care if I see another
cop car as long as I live.
In fact, I'm gonna give you
boys a whole bunch of money.
You like naked girls? I'm
gonna get you some Playboys.
And some candy. You like candy?
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(SHERIFF KRETZER GRUNTING)
(COUGHS)
(SNIFFS)
(GRUNTING)
HARRISON OVER RADIO: Hello?
Is mere anybody there?
Hello, Mr. Sheriff.
My friend and I have your car,
and we're real sorry.
We don't want to get in trouble
but we don't know
how to get back.
And we're real scared.
We're out here all alone.
Whew. (SNIFFS)
Well, you boys sure had me.
(LAUGHING)
Okay. All right.
All right, nothing to
worry about now.
What's important is that
we get you boys home safe.
Now, you didn't
touch anything, did you?
A lot of dangerous
equipment in my car.
You didn't open the
trunk there, did you?
HARRISON: No.
Okay. That's good.
(LAUGHS) That's good.
Now, I want you to go ahead and sit
yourselves down in the backseat.
Don't touch anything.
Anybody comes by,
you just say,
"Help is on the way."
You're doing a real special job
guarding the car for the
sheriff, do you understand?
HARRISON: Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Now, you say that you don't
know how to get home.
Do you know where you are,
what street you're on?
No.
Well, take a look around.
You see any street signs?
No.
All right. Okay.
Well, the road that you're
on, is it a dirt road?
No.
Good. Good.
Now tell me,
is it a hilly road?
Huh';?
Is it a hilly road
or is it a flat road?
Flat.
Okay. All right.
Now take a look around.
You see any houses?
Anything at all that
might help me find you?
I see some windmills.
A windmill?
Well, uh... That's great.
That's great.
You know what?
I think I know
where to find you.
What's your name, son?
Harrison.
And you, Time partner mere,
what's his name?
Travis.
You boys did
the right thing calling me.
You just sit tight,
help is on the way.
And don't You worry.
You are not in any
kind of trouble. In.
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLING)
Stop fidgeting,
you little shit.
That gun doesn't even work!
(GUNSHOT) (SCREAMS)
That's right.
Look. Shh!
He can't hear us.
(WHISPERS) What's he doing?
TRAVIS: I don't know.
HARRISON: Maybe he's looking
to go to the bathroom.
I hate him.
I think he's trying to hide.
He sucks at hiding.
HARRISON: Why does
he need both guns?
TRAVIS: He's a gun hog.
Here he comes.
(KEYS JANGLING)
(ENGINE STARTS) (PANTING)
Where are we going?
Are we going home?
Hey!
This sucks.
Yeah, this
fucking sucks.
(RATTLING)
Where'd he go?
He's hiding.
(GUNSHOT)
He's gonna shoot us!
Maybe he won't.
Okay. Now, the man that owns this
car is gonna be here real soon.
You understand?
And when he gets here, I need you
boys to do something for me.
Okay?
You can't tell him
where I'm hiding.
He can't even know I'm here.
He's got to think
I'm still in the trunk.
Why? Shut up!
Just do what I said,
just keep quiet.
'Cause if you don't, you
know what I'll have to do?
Shoot us?
No, I won't.
What I will do is...
You got a mom and dad?
My grandma.
You got a pet?
A guinea pig-
You?
Snake and a dog.
You live with your mom or dad?
My mom and my step-dad.
What I'll do is
go by your house,
and first I'll kill your dog.
I'll take a hammer,
hit him in the head
until the hammer's
covered in brains.
And then I'll take
that snake of yours,
and I'll slit him open
top to bottom.
Then, your mom, well, she'll
probably have heard that,
and she'll wonder,
"What's going on?"
And when I see her, you
know what I'll do to her?
Shoot her in the face.
And your step-dad, too.
Make both their faces
into ground beef.
And you, I'll take that,
what you call ii, guinea pig.
And I'll throw him against
the ground as hard as I can.
But that probably
won't kill him,
and so while he's squirming around
down there, down in the dirt,
I'll stomp him with my boot.
Crush that guinea pig of yours.
And your grandma,
I'll slit her throat
with a big ol' knife.
And she'll scream for you,
"Come and help me."
But no sound will come out.
And you want to know why?
'Cause you can't scream
with a slit throat.
You understand?
So, when the sheriff shows up
looking for his car'
what are we gonna do?
Be quiet.
Great.
You're eating a Slim Jim now?
(WHISPERS) No. Look.
Next time he comes back,
you should shoot him.
Here he comes.
Shoot him.
Why didn't you shoot him?
You do it.
(ENGINE IDLING)
(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
Should we tell?
(WHISPERS) What if this
guy kills our families?
He just wants his car back.
I don't know.
Fuck! Fuck!
Whew. (LAUGHING)
You boys sure gave me a fright.
Holy hell.
Whew. (SNIFFS)
What do you say we
get you home safe, huh?
(SNIFFS)
Okay, now you boys
answer me now.
Did you open up the trunk?
Was there somebody
inside the trunk?
Did you open the trunk?
Boy, you answer me now,
or I will shoot you dead,
right through this door.
Tell me right now.
Where is he?
Son.
I am the only person out here
that you can trust.
I am the only one
that can help you.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(WHISPERS) Oh, fuck.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
(TURNS STEREO OFF)
I knew it!
You little shit!
I knew I wasn't crazy!
You think you could
run down this highway
and I won't know about it?
I know these roads
like the back of my hand!
What's wrong with you?
Don't think you can play dumb with me.
I saw you.
You almost ran me off the road.
You are in so much trouble!
Get out of the car!
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Step outside the car. Come on.
Get out! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
SHERIFF KRETZER: Ma'am.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna need you
to calm down.
I'm a police officer.
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Are you bleeding'?
I'm so...
Ma'am! What?
I'm gonna need you lo
stop talking, all right?
Okay. Okay. All right?
Just nod your head. Okay.
Just nod. Just nod it at me.
Okay. All right.
I've been injured
by a perpetrator.
He is the father of the two boys
that are inside this vehicle.
You are okay.
He has fled the scene,
and everything is okay,
but I'm gonna need your help
with something. All right?
Now, listen up.
After I was attacked,
he threw my keys
on the other side of the road,
way over there.
And what I'm gonna need you to
do is go ahead, cross the road,
and see if you can
find my keys for me
so that I can radio
for assistance.
You see, I cannot walk.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Why don't I just call somebody
to come and get you'?
No. No, no.
No need to call.
Just head on over there
and see what you can find.
Go on. Go on.
You okay? Yeah.
Go on.
Okay.
Just take a good
look around there.
BEV: It's gonna be hard
to find them out here.
There's so much tumbleweed.
SHERIFF KRETZER: Cover as
much ground as you can.
Yeah, and just keep
your eyes peeled, okay?
Okay? Okay!
SHERIFF KRETZER: Are you
the woman that reported
the children
driving the cruiser?
Yeah. Yeah, that was me.
Everyone said that
I seen it wrong,
but I knew I saw them.
Well, you did
a real good thing, ma'am.
It's citizens like you that make
a difference in our community.
Taking an active role.
BEV: I don't see anything.
SHERIFF KRETZER:
You didn't find anything?
Nothing at all?
Keep looking.
Oh, my God.
There's a man out there!
(GUNSHOT)
(BOYS SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(THUD)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
HARRISON: Help! TRAVIS: Help!
Help!
(GRUNTING)
Help! Help!
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH CRYING SOFTLY)
What time do you think it is?
(BOTH SNIFFLING)
I don't know.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
We have to go.
I think they're dead.
I was gonna try to
shoot out the window.
Dang it, how do these work?
Let me try.
(WHISPERS) Come on.
Try like...
Try to smash
the window with it.
(GRUNTING)
Let me throw it.
(GROANS)
If this would just...
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
How'd you do that?
I don't know!
MY ears!
(CRYING)
Oh.
Wait!
I think something hit me.
You should've worn
the bulletproof vest.
(WHISPERS) I know.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Where's the lights?
It's by the shifter thing.
It's not working!
It's okay. It doesn't
hurt much anymore.
SHERIFF KRETZER:
(OVER RADIO) Boys.
(WEAKLY) Boys.
I know you can hear me.
Slow down, boys.
It's all right,
I just...
I just want my car back.
Son of a bitch.
You don't...
(SCREAMS)
Steal...
A fucking...
Cop car!
COW MOOS
(TIRES SCREECHING)
We did it! Travis!
(PANTING)
(WHISPERS) Just take me
home quick. Quick.
(SIREN WAILING)
FEMALE DISPATCHER: (ON RADIO)
Sheriff, you out there?
Sheriff, can you hear me?
Do you copy?
This is Dispatch.
I think there's
no one out there.
Hello!
(MUSIC PLAYING)